people all the time. They help people
all all the time. Old people. But for 5
years, he didn't have a
boyfriend. So what happened to the
karma? Where's the karma?
Uh you plant a karma. How do you plant a
karma? When you go to visit the old
person or the young person who is
lonely, when you go there, you plant
karma.
How karma is planted in your own mind. I
cannot plant your karma. You have to
plant your own karma. If you want to
make $200 million or you want to be a
yoga teacher or or you want to have a
nice partner, you have to plan. I cannot
do for you. If I could do, I will do
from America. I don't have to fly here.
You
see, you have to plant your own karma.
How? You must visit lonely person
yourself. How does the karma come into
your mind? How does the seed come into
your mind? You are watching yourself
with your own eyes. Okay? You are go to
the old person's house. You are talking
to them. Tell me about your when you
were young. Tell me some story from your
life. They will tell you the same story
every week because they forgot they told
you before. Okay, I'm similar. Then
[Music]
uh when you help them, when you visit
them, when you're helping them and nice
to them, who is
[Music]
watching? They are watching and you are
watching. Your mind, your eyes are like
a camera, like there's this video
camera, right? So when you talking to
the old person you are hearing yourself
this plants a seed okay when you do
something good you are watching yourself
and that puts a seed in your mind okay
that's how you get a
seed then think you can say I have many
friends they helped their grandmother
they helped their grandfather they
didn't get a boyfriend then what
happened to the karma the karma is there
nothing can Stop coming. Nothing. If you
have somebody, good thing will happen to
you 10 times more, 20 times more, 30
times more, 200 million times more. It
will come back. Okay? Otherwise, you
give $10 and $10 come back. It's a waste
of time. Okay? The seed is small, right?
This tree, this tree started from a seed
that you can hold in your hand. Now that
tree can can break the house. If it
falls down, it will break that building.
You know, it came from this seed this
big. The seed in the mind is the same.
Okay. Plant the small seed for a nice
partner.
beautiful partner will come much much
you give the old person one hour a week
and then a man or a woman will come into
your life for your whole life and more
beautiful every year why you planted the
seed how big was the seed one
hour how big is the the boyfriend or the
girlfriend who comes out of the seed
whole life okay it's it's the nature of
seed small seed big tree. Okay, you just
have to plant it, then relax. Okay,
everyone's so uptight. I have to have a
boyfriend. I couldn't find a man. Relax.
Just plant a seed. Plant a seed, then
relax. Okay, then he has to come. He
doesn't have choice. Okay, he will come.
I'm not kidding. I planted many seeds
for money. I quit the business in 1999.
I stopped working. I don't do the
business anymore. Then I took yoga
class. uh Dharma Midra in New York. I
went to big yoga teacher. He kills you
for 2 hours. But afterward you can tell
your friends I went to
Dharma and uh he kills you. Then one guy
came up to me in the class. He said you
are I said yeah. He said I want to shake
your head. I said okay thanks. He said
okay bye. Then I said wait what's your
name? John. Then I never met him in my
life. I never met him. Then that day I
got email in the
evening. Why didn't you thank me? John
from John. Why didn't you thank me? Then
I wrote him email. Why? Why should I
thank you? You Michael, you have I have
a rock bag I carry with me. He said, you
look inside. Then I look inside. There's
an envelope. Look in the envelope.
there's a check
$100,000 US. Then I'm
like, then I sent an email, you
know, thank
you. Then I said, why you give me money?
I don't know you. I never met you in my
life. Why you give me money? He says, I
also don't know why. I just want to give
you you know it means I planted the seed
before then even I don't want money the
money will chase me okay I'm running
money is running faster when it comes
really I'm not kidding who who will give
you $100 in yoga class it's it's strange
you know if you plant a seed for a good
partner they will come they don't have a
choice they must come okay it's very
Beautiful. But you have to take good
care of the seed. All right? You must
know how to plant the seed. If I have a
what do you call watermelon seed and I
throw it here, will it grow? It won't
grow. Is it a good seed? Yeah, it is a
good seed. You put in the wrong place.
You don't know how to take care of the
seed. Don't put water. Don't put soil.
No sunlight. How can it grow? It won't
grow. Okay. All of the karma in you have
uh 20 million 200 million karma in your
mind already. You already have everybody
here has you have the
seeds. You helped many people and you
helped many old people. Everybody you
did some good things in your life. The
seeds are there but there's no water.
Okay, I will teach you the water.
Okay, there's a special meditation they
can teach you. John can teach you, Lean
can teach you. It's called we call
coffee meditation. Okay, coffee
meditation you can do like this,
right? Then you
can that's not coffee. Okay, don't do
that. My teacher taught me, he said, go
like
[Music]
this. This is
meditation. Then I said to my teacher,
that's not meditation. He said, it is
meditation. Then I said, where do you do
it? He said, on your
bed. Then when before you go to sleep,
then what am I supposed to think about?
Think about the old woman which you
helped today. You took her to the coffee
shop, right? I take my old lady to I'm
going to give her the Norwegian sweater
in the coffee shop. Okay, I will take
her to coffee. She dresses up. She puts
on her makeup. We go out. Then I say,
"Come to the coffee shop. I have sweater
for you." You know and then when you
come
home you have a scene in your mind who
put it there.
You did
how you were there when you gave the
sweater. Okay. That's all your mind is
that video camera. It makes them see in
your mind. Then go home, eat your
dinner, clean up, take your bath, then
lay down on your bed and say, "Oh, today
I did a good thing." What? I took the
old lady to the coffee shop. I gave her,
what's it called? Dale of Norway. Yeah.
Dale of Norway. Dale of Norway. Dale of
Norway. I gave her Dale of Norway
sweater. I will not tell her it was 50%
discount. Then uh it has a price big
price tag. Then uh she was so happy and
she put on the sweater and she's looking
in the mirror and when I think about her
and I think about how happy she was.
This is the water on the karma. This is
the for the seed. The karma seed.
There's water on the seed and it will
grow faster. It will grow very fast and
then you will have a beautiful
relationship. Okay, that's all. Okay,
people don't know how to put water on
the karma. Now you know where
on the bed
when before you go to
sleep. What kind of meditation? Think
about the people you helped today. Think
about what good thing you did today.
This is water on the karma. then $200
million will come. Okay, I'm not
kidding. You can check. We own
jewelry.com. The name cost $21 million.
The name jewelry.com cost $21 million.
Okay, how? Just
relax. Think about the good thing that
you did for other people and that makes
the seat go fast. Okay. Is it difficult?
It's easier than yoga, right? Okay.
Okay. All right, then I'm telling you
big secret. This is $200 million secret
or boyfriend secret. Okay, you can plant
that. You don't have to work so hard.
Help somebody else to get the secret you
want. Then come home, do this
meditation. We call in Tibetan we call
shea. Say she
didn't just do that. Didn't the
boyfriend you you can't run away from
the boyfriend. He will chase you. All
right. I'm not kidding. Okay. Uh I
thought we take a break, but I have a
question for
you. We will take a break. It's okay,
Joe? Yeah. Uh but I have a question for
you. Uh someone asked me in China, when
I was in China, they asked a very good
question. One guy raised his hand and he
said, "I I understand your system. It
sounds good to me. It's logical. If I
help someone to who is
lonely, it plants karma for boyfriend.
If I help poor people, money will come
to me. I like your system. It sounds
good to me. But in China, when we are
young, our mother, our father, they will
tell us, "Help other people. Do good for
other people. But don't ask them for
something. Give me something. This is
not love. I This is not love. This is
business. Oh, I will take you to the
coffee shop. I will give you a sweater
from Dale of Norway if if I get a
boyfriend. If I get a girlfriend. It's
like a business, right? Or I will help
the poor people. Why? I want more money.
You see, this is not love. This is like
strange, selfish. I want something from
you so I will be nice to you.
Then I Chinese person asked me this this
sounds strange to Chinese people our
mother our father told us when you give
something to somebody or you help the
old person do it from love don't ask
them for something you know don't say
give me now give me something it should
be from love okay so what is my answer
for
that after refreshments okay there's
something very interesting
Okay, there's something very
interesting. If you understand how to
plant seed, if you understand this new
system, when you use it, you help the
whole world. You are helping the whole
world. You are making peace in the
world. You are helping everybody in the
world. If you take the old woman to the
coffee shop and give her a sweater from
Dale of
Norway, you are helping the whole world.
You are making peace in the world. Why?
How? I'm not going to tell
you. After refreshments, it's a we call
blackmailing. You have to come back.
Okay. Then no. In the second half, we
have to talk about this uh question,
right?
How to make peace in the world by using
this system. We talk about that. Okay.